Guide to the George Dudley Seymour Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1831-1944; Series I; 11.5; (35 boxes)
  - Rogers, James Gamble(*), 1921-1938 (Box 25, Folder 248)
    See also: box 73, folder 1078
  - Rom - Ry (Box 25, Folder 249)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore(*), 1911 (Box 25, Folder 249A)
  - Sab - Sc (Box 25, Folder 250-251)
  - Sec - Seymour, E (Box 26, Folder 252)
  - Seymour, Charles(*), 1910-1944, undated (Box 26, Folder 253)
    See also: box 37, folder 398
  - Seymour, F - J(*) (Box 26, Folder 254)
  - Seymour, L - O(*) (Box 26, Folder 255)
  - Seymour, Laura(*), 1894-1937, undated (Box 26, Folder 256-257)
  - Seymour, R - Sexton (Box 26, Folder 258)
  - Seymour, William(*), 1937-1944 (Box 26, Folder 259-260)
  - Sha - Shi (Box 27, Folder 261)
  - Shepard, James(*), 1894-1925 (Box 27, Folder 262)
  - Shipman, Arthur L., Jr.(*), 1910-1943, undated (Box 27, Folder 263)
    See also: box 39, folder 455 See also: box 85, folder 1262
  - Sho - Stok (Box 27, Folder 264-268)
  - Stiles, Wallace(*), 1917-1944, undated (Box 27, Folder 269)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps(*), 1906-1941, undated (Box 28, Folder 270)
  - Stokes, Carol (Mrs. Anson P.), 1917-1926 (Box 28, Folder 270)
  - Ston - Sy (Box 28, Folder 271)
  - Stone, Elizabeth B.(*), 1921-1940, undated (Box 28, Folder 272-273)
  - Strickland, Emily M.(*), 1918-1943, undated (Box 28, Folder 274)
    See also: box 53, folder 705-708
  - Tac - Taf (Box 28, Folder 275)
  - Taft, Horace D.(*), 1912-1938 (Box 28, Folder 276-278)
  - Taft, William Howard(*), 1903-1915 (Box 28, Folder 279)
    See also: box 104, folder 1493 See also: box 116, folder 25
  - Taft, William Howard(*), 1916-1930 (Box 29, Folder 280-285A)
  - Tal - Tha (Box 29, Folder 286)
  - Talcott, Mary K.(*), 1905-1917 (Box 29, Folder 287)
    See also: box 39, folder 460-464
  - Tho - Tou (Box 29, Folder 288-289)
  - Tinker, Chauncey Brewster(*), 1913-1934 (Box 30, Folder 290)
  - Tow - U (Box 30, Folder 291-293)
  - Updike, Daniel Berkeley(*), 1913-1939 (Box 30, Folder 294)
  - Va (Box 30, Folder 295)
  - Van DeVanter, Willis(*), 1928-1936 (Box 30, Folder 295A)
  - Ve - Vo (Box 30, Folder 296)
  - W - Wal (Box 30, Folder 297)
  - War - Wat (Box 30, Folder 298)
  - We - Weir (Box 30, Folder 299)
  - Weir, John Ferguson, and Weir, May (Mrs. John)(*), 1894-1925 (Box 30, Folder 300)
  - Weit - Welch, H (Box 31, Folder 301)
  - Welch, Lewis S.(*), 1906-1938, undated (Box 31, Folder 302-304)
    See also: box 82, folder 1212
  - Welch, M. - Wey(*) (Box 31, Folder 305)
  - Welles, Edwin Stanley(*), 1910-1944 (Box 31, Folder 306)
    See also: box 39, folder 473 See also:box 45, folder 560-561 See also: box 46, folder 581 See also: box 84, folder 1242
  - Welles, Horace L.(*), 1895-1906 (Box 31, Folder 307)
  - Welles, Lemuel Aiken(*), 1917-1944 (Box 31, Folder 308)
    See also: box 39, folder 474
  - Welles, Roger and Harriet(*), 1883-1931 (Box 31, Folder 309)
  - Wha - White (Box 32, Folder 310)
  - Wheeler, George W.(*), 1909-1916, undated (Box 32, Folder 311)
  - Whitf - Whitn (Box 32, Folder 312)
  - Whitney, Margaret D.(*), [ca. (Box 32, Folder 313)
  - Whitt - Wille (Box 32, Folder 314)
  - Wilder, Amos P.(*), 1915-1936 (Box 32, Folder 315)
  - Willi - Wy (Box 32, Folder 316-318)
  - Y - Z (Box 33, Folder 319)
  - Unidentified (Box 33, Folder 320)
  - Unidentified post cards and greeting cards (Box 33, Folder 321)
  - Letter copy books, 1914 January - 1916 March (Box 34, Folder 322-323)
  - Letter copy books, 1916 April - 1919 November (Box 35, Folder 324-325)
- Family Genealogy, 1709-1943; Series II; 6.75; (17 boxes)
  This series contains the correspondence, photographs, documents, papers, and miscellanea Seymour compiled in the course of his extensive research on the genealogy and history of his family.
  The series is arranged in the following sections: Seymour family, Churchill family, Welles family, Other families, Miscellaneous papers, Sermons, and Photographs.
  - Seymour family
    - Family correspondence
      - Allen, Irene, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 326)
        See also: box 1, folder 10
      - Angell, Elizabeth D.S., 1937 (Box 36, Folder 327)
      - Barker, M.E., 1932-1939, undated (Box 36, Folder 328)
      - Bradley, Katharine E., undated (Box 36, Folder 329)
      - Bradley, Marion Ogden, 1932-1936 (Box 36, Folder 330)
      - Briggs, Herbert, 1913-1915 (Box 36, Folder 331)
      - Brooker, Charles F., 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 332)
      - Bull, Jonathan and William, 1785 (Box 36, Folder 333)
      - Burlington, Janet, 1908 (Box 36, Folder 334)
      - Camp, Charles L.N., 1916 (Box 36, Folder 335)
      - Carrington, George M., 1893 (Box 36, Folder 336)
      - Chapman, Robert and Francis Sage: deed, 1803 (Box 36, Folder 337)
      - Comstock, Howard Seymour and Olga N., 1935 (Box 36, Folder 338)
      - Conkling, Julia Catherine Seymour, 1890-1993, undated (Box 36, Folder 339)
      - Cowles, W.D., 1896 (Box 36, Folder 340)
      - Dana, Richard H., Jr., 1931 (Box 36, Folder 341)
      - Day, Katharine Seymour, 1913-1917, undated (Box 36, Folder 342)
      - Day, Robert E., 1892 (Box 36, Folder 343)
      - Dickinson, Rose Ledyard, 1931-1936 (Box 36, Folder 344)
      - Dix, Ethel M., 1929 (Box 36, Folder 345)
      - Doolittle, Lana Seymour (Mrs. Charles), 1936-1937 (Box 36, Folder 346)
      - Dwight, Rae Seymour, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 347)
      - Dyer, Margaret Comstock, 1935-1936 (Box 36, Folder 348)
      - Edgerton, Seymour, 1913-1914 (Box 36, Folder 349)
      - Eulls, Emma S., 1917 (Box 36, Folder 350)
      - Fairchild, Helen Lincklaen, 1890-1915 (Box 36, Folder 351-352)
      - Ferry, Mansfield, 1936-1937 (Box 36, Folder 353)
      - Flagg, Ernest, 1917, 1927 (Box 36, Folder 354)
      - Galland, Clarissa Seymour, 1881, undated (Box 36, Folder 355)
      - Garmany, Caroline Day Bissell, 1936, undated (Box 36, Folder 356)
      - Gay, Catherine (Mrs. Frederic Parker), 1937 (Box 36, Folder 357)
      - Goodsell, Katharine Seymour Jackson, 1934 (Box 36, Folder 358)
      - Hastings, (Mrs.) Thomas Seymour, 1936 (Box 36, Folder 359)
      - Havens, May Catherine, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 360)
      - Hill, Mary Pelham, 1936-1939 (Box 36, Folder 361)
      - Hooker, John: deed, 1756 (Box 36, Folder 362)
      - Hough, Huldah R., 1881, 1891 (Box 36, Folder 363)
      - Huntington, Abigail, 1938-1939, undated (Box 36, Folder 364)
      - Ingraham, Dudley Seymour and Marion Morton, 1935-1941 (Box 36, Folder 365)
      - Ingraham, Edward, 1932-1943 (Box 36, Folder 366)
      - Ingraham, William S., 1914 (Box 36, Folder 367)
      - Jackson, Alice Day, undated (Box 36, Folder 368)
      - Jackson, John Day and Rose, 1913-1936 (Box 36, Folder 369)
      - Jackson, Joseph C., Jr., 1914 (Box 36, Folder 370)
      - Jewell, Amy Seymour, 1886 (Box 37, Folder 371)
      - Kellogg, Martin, 1788, 1790 (Box 37, Folder 372)
      - Knap, Thomas Seymour, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 373)
      - Leggett, M. D., 1878 (Box 37, Folder 374)
      - Loomis, Ellen Seymour Hanson, 1897, undated (Box 37, Folder 375)
      - Loomis, Archibald G., 1916 (Box 37, Folder 375)
      - Lyman, Wyllys, 1893 (Box 37, Folder 376)
      - Malin, Louisa Seymour, 1938 (Box 37, Folder 377)
      - Morris, Seymour; Morris, Ida; Morris, Seymour Tucker, 1917-1940 (Box 37, Folder 378)
      - Nash, James R., 1931 (Box 37, Folder 379)
      - Parsons, Francis, 1935 (Box 37, Folder 380)
      - Parsons, Harriet Day, 1934-1936, undated (Box 37, Folder 381)
      - Parsons, William E., 1936-1937 (Box 37, Folder 382)
      - Peck family, 1937-1938, undated (Box 37, Folder 383)
      - Perry, James DeWolf and Edith Weir (Box 37, Folder 384)
      - Pinney, Maria Watson and Royal W., 1894, 1936, undated (Box 37, Folder 385)
      - Pomeroy, Cornelia R., 1901 (Box 37, Folder 386)
      - Raymond, Mary W., 1934 (Box 37, Folder 387)
      - Remington, Jane S. L., 1935-1936 (Box 37, Folder 388)
      - Roe, D. H., 1895 (Box 37, Folder 389)
      - Sage, Francis (Box 37, Folder 389)
        See: box 36, folder 337
      - St. John, Clara Seymour, 1931, 1937 (Box 37, Folder 390)
      - St. John, Samuel, 1815 (Box 37, Folder 391)
      - Sanford, Daniel S., 1936 (Box 37, Folder 392)
      - Seymour, Albert Allen, undated (Box 37, Folder 393)
      - Seymour, Arthur Bliss, 1907-1917 (Box 37, Folder 394)
      - Seymour, C. J., 1880-1991 (Box 37, Folder 395)
      - Seymour, Carlton, 1880, 1913 (Box 37, Folder 396)
      - Seymour, Charles and Gladys, 1913-1940, undated (Box 37, Folder 397)
        See also: box 26, folder 253
      - Seymour, Charles M., 1933 (Box 37, Folder 398)
      - Seymour, Charlotte S., 1931 (Box 37, Folder 399)
      - Seymour, Clarence William, 1914-1938 (Box 37, Folder 400)
      - Seymour, Daniel, 1845-1846, 1936 (Box 37, Folder 401)
      - Seymour, Edward, 1796 (Box 37, Folder 402)
      - Seymour, Eli, 1793 (Box 37, Folder 403)
      - Seymour, Estella M., 1921 (Box 37, Folder 404)
      - Seymour, Florelle Putnam, 1914 (Box 37, Folder 405)
      - Seymour, George de Villess, 1884 (Box 37, Folder 406)
      - Seymour, George Franklin, 1891, 1897 (Box 37, Folder 407)
      - Seymour, George Steele, 1923 (Box 37, Folder 408)
      - Seymour, H. F., 1931 (Box 37, Folder 409)
      - Seymour, Harriet, 1917-1938 (Box 37, Folder 410)
      - Seymour, Helena E., 1893 (Box 37, Folder 411)
      - Seymour, Henry, 1791, 1796 (Box 37, Folder 412)
      - Seymour, Henry A. (Albert), 1842-1843, 1897 (Box 37, Folder 413-414)
      - Seymour, Henry Albert, Jr., 1871-1881, 1917 (Box 37, Folder 415)
      - Seymour, Henry T., 1915 (Box 37, Folder 416)
      - Seymour, Henry W., 1891-1904, undated (Box 38, Folder 417-421)
      - Seymour, Horace, 1881 (Box 38, Folder 422)
      - Seymour, Horace S., 1913 (Box 38, Folder 423)
      - Seymour, Horatio, 1868 (Box 38, Folder 424)
      - Seymour, Horatio, Jr., 1913 (Box 38, Folder 425)
      - Seymour, Horatio Winslow, 1914 (Box 38, Folder 426)
      - Seymour, John Sammis, 1896 (Box 38, Folder 427)
      - Seymour, Julius H., 1913 (Box 38, Folder 428)
      - Seymour, (Mrs.) L. W., 1925 (Box 38, Folder 429)
      - Seymour, M. E., 1908 (Box 38, Folder 430)
      - Seymour, M. Louise, 1919 (Box 38, Folder 431)
      - Seymour, Mabel G., 1938 (Box 38, Folder 432)
      - Seymour, Malcolm, 1927 (Box 38, Folder 433)
      - Seymour, Morris W., 1890-1919, undated (Box 38, Folder 434)
      - Seymour, N. Gilbert, 1935-1939 (Box 38, Folder 435)
      - Seymour, Noah: autograph fragment, 1812 (Box 38, Folder 436)
      - Seymour, Origen Storrs, 1931-1939 (Box 38, Folder 437)
      - Seymour, R., undated (Box 38, Folder 438)
      - Seymour, Falph Richard, 1932-1936 (Box 38, Folder 439-440)
      - Seymour, Sarah A., 1940 (Box 38, Folder 441)
      - Seymour, Storrs Ozias (Rev.), 1890-1917 (Box 38, Folder 442)
      - Seymour, Theodore P., 1932-1939 (Box 38, Folder 443)
      - Seymour, Thomas (1668-1740), 1725, 1733 (Box 38, Folder 444)
      - Seymour, Thomas (1705-1767), 1761, 1764-1765, undated (Box 38, Folder 445)
      - Seymour, Thomas (1735-1829), 1768-1769, 1773, 1790, 1809, 1816 (Box 38, Folder 446)
      - Seymour, Thomas Day, 1889-1897, undated (Box 38, Folder 447)
      - Seymour, Thomas Hart, 1852-1866, undated (Box 38, Folder 448)
      - Seymour, Thomas S., 1805 (Box 38, Folder 449)
      - Seymour, Truman, 1872 (Box 38, Folder 450)
      - Seymour, W. B., 1913-1914 (Box 38, Folder 451)
      - Seymour, William, 1844 (Box 38, Folder 452)
      - Seymour, William H., 1896 (Box 38, Folder 453)
      - Seymour-Holm, Phyllis, 1937 (Box 39, Folder 454)
      - Shipman, Arthur L., Jr., 1934-1938 (Box 39, Folder 455)
        See also: box 27, folder 263 See also: box 85, folder 1262
      - Shull, George H., 1931 (Box 39, Folder 456)
      - Steele, Thomas M., 1938 (Box 39, Folder 457)
      - Stone, Harriet, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 458)
      - Swift, (Mrs.) Charles, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 459)
      - Talcott, Mary Kingsbury, 1866-1917, 1931, undated (Box 39, Folder 460-464)
        See also: box 29, folder 287
      - Talcott, Mary T., Circa 1890s (Box 39, Folder 465)
      - Toy, Mary Seymour, 1914 (Box 39, Folder 466)
      - Treadway, Morton Candee, undated (Box 39, Folder 467)
      - Treadway, William Ingraham, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 468)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 39, Folder 469)
      - Vadakin, Ann Seymour, 1909 (Box 39, Folder 470)
      - Vaill, Dudley L., 1916 (Box 39, Folder 471)
      - Watts, Elizabeth Jackson, 1914, 1933 (Box 39, Folder 472)
      - Welles, Edwin Stanley, 1898-1942 (Box 39, Folder 473)
        See also: box 31, folder 306 See also: box 45, folder 560-561 See also: box 46, folder 581 See also: box 84, folder 1242
      - Welles, Lemuel A., 1939 (Box 39, Folder 474)
        See also: box 31, folder 308 See also: box 46, folder 582
      - Wiley, Helen Seymour, 1936, undated (Box 39, Folder 475)
      - Wiley, James Seymour, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 476)
      - Wilson, Mabel Johnson, 1936 (Box 39, Folder 477)
      - Wright, R. P., 1914 (Box 39, Folder 478)
    - Family papers
      - Pensions: copies (Box 40, Folder 479-480)
      - Records (Box 40, Folder 481)
      - Seal (Box 40, Folder 482)
      - Wills and estate inventories: copies (Box 40, Folder 483-484)
    - Non-family correspondence
      - A (Box 41, Folder 485)
      - B (Box 41, Folder 486)
      - Bartlett, J. Gardner, 1915-1917 (Box 41, Folder 487)
      - Bates, Alfred, 1924-1938 (Box 41, Folder 488)
      - Brainard, Morgan Bulkeley, 1931-1936 (Box 41, Folder 489)
      - C (Box 41, Folder 490)
      - Connecticut State Library, 1893-1938 (Box 41, Folder 491)
      - D (Box 41, Folder 492)
      - E-F (Box 41, Folder 493)
      - G (Box 41, Folder 494)
      - H (Box 41, Folder 495)
      - Jacobus, Donald Lines, 1917, 1931-1939, undated (Box 41, Folder 496-498)
      - K-L (Box 41, Folder 499)
      - M (Box 41, Folder 500)
      - N (Box 41, Folder 501)
      - New England Historic Genealogical Society, 1917, 1935, 1939 (Box 41, Folder 502)
      - P-R (Box 41, Folder 503)
      - S (Box 41, Folder 504)
      - T (Box 41, Folder 505)
      - U-V (Box 41, Folder 506)
      - Unidentified (Box 41, Folder 507)
      - W (Box 41, Folder 508)
      - Y (Box 41, Folder 509)
    - Writings, research materials, and miscellanea
      - Bible: origin of family bible, undated (Box 42, Folder 510)
      - Clippings, 1920s (Box 42, Folder 511-512)
      - Furniture, undated (Box 42, Folder 513)
    - Genealogy
      - Ancestral tablets, 1920s (Box 42, Folder 514)
      - Drafts and essays
        - General, undated (Box 42, Folder 515)
        - "Brief sketch of the Life of Henry Albert Seymour", undated (Box 42, Folder 516)
        - "The English Home and Ancestry of Richard Seymour of Hartford, Connecticut", undated (Box 42, Folder 517-518)
        - "Father's Reminiscences of the Spencer and Seymour Families", 1894 (Box 42, Folder 519)
        - "Richard Seymour...", undated (Box 42, Folder 520)
        - "The Rise and Fall of the Great Tradition", undated (Box 42, Folder 521-522)
        - "The Seymour Family in America" (Box 42, Folder 521-522)
      - Printed material, 1880-1939 (Box 42, Folder 523-525)
      - Research notes
        - General, undated (Box 43, Folder 526-529)
        - "A Records of the Seymour Family in the Revolution", undated (Box 43, Folder 530)
        - Talcott, Mary Kingsbury, undated (Box 43, Folder 531)
      - Miscellanea, undated (Box 43, Folder 532-533)
  - Churchill family
    - Correspondence and papers
      - A-B (Box 44, Folder 534)
      - Account book: unidentified, undated (Box 44, Folder 535)
      - C (Box 44, Folder 536)
      - Churchill, Charles(1723-1802)
        - Correspondence, 1790-1792 (Box 44, Folder 537)
        - Deed, 1787 (Box 44, Folder 538)
        - Militia compact, 1775 (Box 44, Folder 539)
        - Orders and letter, 1780 (Box 44, Folder 540)
      - Churchill, Charles(1790-1845), 1820-1834 (Box 44, Folder 541)
      - Churchill, Chester, 1822, 1825 (Box 44, Folder 542)
      - Churchill, John, 1807, undated (Box 44, Folder 543)
      - Churchill, John(?), undated (Box 44, Folder 544)
      - Churchill, Joseph, 1725 (Box 44, Folder 545)
      - Churchill, Julia, 1847-1868 (Box 44, Folder 546)
      - Churchill, Lucretia Olmstead, 1828-1875 (Box 44, Folder 547)
      - Churchill, Mary, 1868-1892, 1903-1907 (Box 44, Folder 548-549)
        See also: box 7, folder 66
      - Churchill, Mary: letters about her property, 1904-1907 (Box 44, Folder 550)
      - Churchill, Samuel, 1833 (Box 44, Folder 551)
      - Churchill, Solomon
        - Correspondence, 1825 (Box 44, Folder 552)
        - Bible, 1789 (Box 44, Folder 553)
      - Churchill estate, 1930-1936 (Box 44, Folder 554)
      - Churchill house, 1915-1929 (Box 44, Folder 555-556)
      - D-I (Box 45, Folder 557)
      - L-T (Box 45, Folder 558)
      - W (Box 45, Folder 559)
      - Welles, Edwin Stanley, 1897-1905, 1916-1942, undated (Box 45, Folder 560-561)
        See also: box 31, folder 306 See also: box 39, folder 473 See also: box 46, folder 581 See also: box 84, folder 1242
      - Willard, Simon, undated (Box 45, Folder 562)
      - Wills and estate inventories: copies (Box 45, Folder 563)
    - Writings, research materials, and miseellanea
      - Clippings (Box 45, Folder 564)
      - Drafts and essays
        - General (Box 45, Folder 565-566)
        - Churchill house: Seymour, George Dudley and Smith, Julia Welles Griswold (Box 45, Folder 567)
        - "Churchill on Churchill family of Wethersfield" (Box 45, Folder 568)
      - Research notes (Box 45, Folder 569-570)
      - Miscellanea
        - Churchill family (Box 45, Folder 571)
        - Churchill house, undated (Box 45, Folder 572)
        - The Jeffersonian: newspapers, edited by Thomas H. Seymour, 1832 (Box 45, Folder 573)
        - Political handbills: Democratic ticket in Connecticut (Origen S. Seymour for Governor), 1874 (Box 45, Folder 574)
  - Welles family
    - Correspondence and papers
      - A-M (Box 46, Folder 575)
      - R-W (Box 46, Folder 576)
      - Sampson, Lilla B., 1904-1936 (Box 46, Folder 577)
      - Unidentified (Box 46, Folder 578)
      - Wells, Abasalom, 1809-1934 (Box 46, Folder 579)
      - Wells, Anne and William: deed, 1770 (Box 46, Folder 580)
      - Welles, Edwin Stanley, 1898-1940 (Box 46, Folder 581)
        See also: box 31, folder 306 See also: box 39, folder 473 See also: box 45, folder 560-561 See also: box 84, folder 1242
      - Welles, Lemuel Aiken, 1891-1930 (Box 46, Folder 582)
        See also: box 31, folder 308
    - Writings, research materials, and miscellanea
      - Clippings (Box 46, Folder 583)
      - Drafts and essays
        - "A Contribution to an Account of the Descendants of Gov. Thomas Welles..." (Box 46, Folder 584-585)
      - Research notes (Box 46, Folder 586)
      - Wills and estate inventories: copies (Box 46, Folder 587)
      - Miscellanea (Box 46, Folder 588)
  - Other families
    - Belden family: Standish, Jared Butler, 1939 (Box 47, Folder 589)
    - Chandler family
      - Correspondence
        - A-B (Box 47, Folder 590)
        - C-K (Box 47, Folder 591)
        - Leavitt, Emily Wilder, 1893-1906 (Box 47, Folder 592)
        - M-W; unidentified (Box 47, Folder 593)
      - Essays (Box 47, Folder 594)
      - Research notes (Box 47, Folder 595)
    - Saltonstall family
      - Correspondence (Box 47, Folder 596)
    - Spencer family
      - Correspondence
        - B-M (Box 47, Folder 597)
        - P-Sumner (Box 47, Folder 598)
        - Starr-W; unidentified (Box 47, Folder 599)
      - Essays (Box 47, Folder 600)
      - Research materials (Box 47, Folder 601)
    - Related families(Tuttle-Goodyear-Winston-Alling-Peck-Standish)
      - Correspondence, 1892-1933, undated (Box 47, Folder 602)
      - Genealogical charts (Box 47, Folder 603)
      - Research notes (Box 47, Folder 604)
  - Miscellaneous papers
    - Andrews, Samuel, 1767 (Box 48, Folder 605)
    - Babcock, Jonathan Wells, 1804 (Box 48, Folder 606)
    - Bills and receipts, [ca1776-1786] (Box 48, Folder 607)
    - Cannon, B. B.: to Olmstead, E., 1840, 1843-1844 (Box 48, Folder 608)
    - Chamberlain, Joanna, 1785 (Box 48, Folder 609)
    - Dubois, Corneli[elligible]s: certificate, Society for the Reformation of Juvenile Delinquency in the city of New York, 1824 (Box 48, Folder 610)
    - Dubois, Henry A.: deed, signed by Martin Van Buren(?), 1838 (Box 48, Folder 611)
    - Edwards, Jonathan(1745-1801): account of funeral (Box 48, Folder 612)
    - Gibbs, William, 1744 (Box 48, Folder 613)
    - Howland, Avery, 1845, undated (Box 48, Folder 614)
    - Howland, Harrison O., 1851 (Box 48, Folder 615)
    - Huntington family, 1793, 1798, 1825, 1840 (Box 48, Folder 616)
    - Hutchinson, Thomas and Sarah: deed, 1724 (Box 48, Folder 617)
    - Morgan family, 1789, 1809 (Box 48, Folder 618)
    - Newell, Samuel, 1747 (Box 48, Folder 619)
    - Sheffield, Joseph E., 1822 (Box 48, Folder 620)
    - Silliman, Benjamin, Jr., 1868, 1884 (Box 48, Folder 621)
    - Steele, Elias M., 1881-1882 (Box 48, Folder 622)
    - Stoughton, Elisha and Lucretia: deed, signed by Oliver Ellsworth, 1787 (Box 48, Folder 623)
    - Tidmarsh, Richard, 1773 (Box 48, Folder 624)
    - Trumbull, Benoni: commission in Hebron, Connecticut, militia, 1729 (Box 48, Folder 625)
    - Winthrop family: document signed by Daniel Wetherell, Recorder of Town Meeting, New London, Connecticut, 1709 (Box 48, Folder 626)
    - Miscellanea, [ca1778-1837], undated (Box 48, Folder 627)
  - Sermons
    - Collins, Daniel, 1776-1779 (Box 48, Folder 628)
    - Cutler, Manasseh, 1822 (Box 48, Folder 629)
    - Huntington, Cornelia Elizabeth: notes, 1824-1825 (Box 48, Folder 630)
    - Jenney, Caleb J.: "Concio and Clerum", 1830 (Box 48, Folder 631)
    - Lathrop, Joseph, 1784, 1790, 1802 (Box 48, Folder 632)
    - Palmer, Ray: "The Voice of the Floods", 1857 (Box 48, Folder 633)
    - Sprague, William B., 1852 (Box 48, Folder 634)
    - Trumbull, Benjamin, 1775, 1776 (Box 48, Folder 635)
  - Photographs
    - Allen, Frederic W. (Box 49, Folder 636)
    - Baldwin, Roger Sherman (Box 49, Folder 637)
    - Churchill family (Box 49, Folder 638-640)
    - Erving, Henry W. (Box 49, Folder 641)
    - Harrington, Evan (Box 49, Folder 642)
    - Hopson, W. F. (Box 49, Folder 643)
    - Ingraham, Edward, II (Box 49, Folder 644)
    - Ingraham, Grace Seymour (Box 49, Folder 645)
    - Ingraham, William Shurtleff (Box 49, Folder 646)
    - Lincklaen, Helen Clarissa Seymour (Box 49, Folder 647)
    - McClung, Lee (Box 49, Folder 648)
    - Mitchell, Ellen Brainard (Box 49, Folder 649)
    - Morris, Charles Newton (Box 49, Folder 650)
    - Peck, Mary Seymour (Box 49, Folder 651)
    - Pinney, Maria Watson (Box 49, Folder 652)
    - Rolanson, Anne Seymour (Box 49, Folder 653)
    - Saltonstall family (Box 49, Folder 654)
    - Seymour, Albert Allen (Box 49, Folder 655)
    - Seymour, Belinda Spencer (Box 49, Folder 655)
    - Seymour, Clarissa (Box 49, Folder 655)
    - Seymour, Electa Churchill (Box 49, Folder 655)
      General
      See also: box 37, folder 415
    - Seymour, George Dudley
      - Youth (Box 49, Folder 656)
      - Young adult (Box 49, Folder 657)
      - Adult (Box 50, Folder 658)
      - European trip, 1895 (Box 50, Folder 659)
      - Home and office, 1883, 1908 (Box 50, Folder 660)
      - Lounsbury, Thomas: funeral, with William Howard Taft and Theodore Roosevelt, 1915 (Box 50, Folder 661)
      - Western United States trip, 1900 (Box 50, Folder 662)
      - Groups
        - General (Box 50, Folder 663)
        - Bristol, Connecticut Centennial, 1885 (Box 50, Folder 664)
    - Seymour, Henry Albert and Electa Churchill: daguerreotypes, glass negative, prints (Box 50, Folder 665)
    - Seymour, Mrs. Israel (Box 50, Folder 666)
    - Seymour, Laura Electa (Box 50, Folder 667)